RG 009:007, Indian Litigation Files
Connecticut State Library
- Series 6. Mohegan, 1848-2006; bulk 1981-2006
  - Maps, 1981
    - Maps
      - Property Map, 40. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 90. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 102. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 107. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 109. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 98. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 49. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 95. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 88. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 103. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 101. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 100. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 99. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 94. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 91. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 96. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 104. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 59. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 30. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 71. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 34. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 12. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 11. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 92. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 77. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 74. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 33. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 82. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 84. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 83. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 108. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 86. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 89. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 81. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 79. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 31. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
      - Property Map, 16. Town of Montville, New London County, Connecticut, 1991 April 22; 1 map, photocopy; Prepared by James W. Sewall Company, Old Town, Maine. (Box 83)
- Series 7. Nipmuc, circa 1745-2007; bulk 1970-2007
  - Legal Documents, 2004-2005
    - Foster and Wheatons Petition 69A submissions, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Nipmuc Petition 69A Request for Reconsideration of the Principal Deputy Assistant Secretary-Indian Affairs' Final Determination Against Federal Acknowledgment - Appendix A, 1-57, 2004 September 23 (Box 16, Folder 23-25)
    - Nipmuc Petition 69A Request for Reconsideration of the Principal Deputy Assistant Secretary-Indian Affairs' Final Determination Against Federal Acknowledgment - Appendix A, 58, 2004 September 23 (Box 16, Folder 26-28)
    - Nipmuc Petition 69A Request for Reconsideration of the Principal Deputy Assistant Secretary-Indian Affairs' Final Determination Against Federal Acknowledgment - Appendix A, 59, 2004 September 23 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Nipmuc Petition 69A Request for Reconsideration of the Principal Deputy Assistant Secretary-Indian Affairs' Final Determination Against Federal Acknowledgment - Appendix A, 60, 2004 September 23 (Box 16, Folder 30-31)
    - Nipmuc Petition 69A Request for Reconsideration of the Principal Deputy Assistant Secretary-Indian Affairs' Final Determination Against Federal Acknowledgment - Appendix A, 61, 2004 September 23 (Box 16, Folder 32-33)
    - Nipmuc Petition 69A Request for Reconsideration of the Principal Deputy Assistant Secretary-Indian Affairs' Final Determination Against Federal Acknowledgment - Appendix A, 62-63, 2004 September 23 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Nipmuc Petition 69A Request for Reconsideration of the Principal Deputy Assistant Secretary-Indian Affairs' Final Determination Against Federal Acknowledgment - Appendix A, 64, 2004 September 23 (Box 17, Folder 2-6)
    - Nipmuc Petition 69A Request for Reconsideration of the Principal Deputy Assistant Secretary-Indian Affairs' Final Determination Against Federal Acknowledgment - Appendix A, 65, 2004 September 23 (Box 17, Folder 7-9)
    - Nipmuc Petition 69A Request for Reconsideration of the Principal Deputy Assistant Secretary-Indian Affairs' Final Determination Against Federal Acknowledgment - Appendix A, 66-109, 2004 September 23 (Box 17, Folder 10-13)
    - Nipmuc Petition 69A Request for Reconsideration of the Principal Deputy Assistant Secretary-Indian Affairs' Final Determination Against Federal Acknowledgment - Appendix B, 110-124, 2004 September 23 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Nipmuc Petition 69A Request for Reconsideration of the Principal Deputy Assistant Secretary-Indian Affairs' Final Determination Against Federal Acknowledgment - Appendix C, 2004 September 23 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Nipmuc Petition 69A Request for Reconsideration of the Principal Deputy Assistant Secretary-Indian Affairs' Final Determination Against Federal Acknowledgment - Appendix D, 2004 September 23 (Box 17, Folder 16-18)
    - Nipmuc Petition 69A Request for Reconsideration of the Principal Deputy Assistant Secretary-Indian Affairs' Final Determination Against Federal Acknowledgment - Appendix E, 2004 September 23 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Nipmuc Petition 69A Request for Reconsideration of the Principal Deputy Assistant Secretary-Indian Affairs' Final Determination Against Federal Acknowledgment - Appendix F, 2004 September 23 (Box 17, Folder 20-21)
    - Nipmuc Petition 69A Request for Reconsideration of the Principal Deputy Assistant Secretary-Indian Affairs' Final Determination Against Federal Acknowledgment - Appendix G, 2004 September 23 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Nipmuc Petition 69A Request for Reconsideration of the Principal Deputy Assistant Secretary-Indian Affairs' Final Determination Against Federal Acknowledgment - Appendix H, 2004 September 23 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Petition 69A & 69B - petition reply brief, 2005 February 3 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Response Brief Regarding Lack of Interested Party Status of Catherine Foster and Kathryn A. Wheaton, 2005 January 27 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Bureau of Indian Affairs, 2000-2007
    - Answer Brief of the State of Connecticut in Opposition to the Request for Reconsideration by the Nipmuc Nation, Petitioner 69A, of the Final Determinatino Against Federal Acknowledgment, 2005 October 6 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs Freedom of Information Act additional response, 2007 September 19 (Box 18, Folder 1-3)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs Freedom of Information Act, Petition 69A, 2007 September 21 (Box 18, Folder 4-6)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs Freedom of Informatin Act responses 1st installment, A.2 to B.85, 2007 May (Box 18, Folder 7-10)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs Freedom of Informatin Act responses 4th installment, 2007 November 5 (Box 18, Folder 11-12)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs Freedom of Information Act responses - Nipmuc 69A, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 13-16)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs Freedom of Information Act responses - Nipmuc 69A, A.13, 2007 September 21 (Box 18, Folder 17-19)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs Freedom of Information Act responses - Nipmuc 69A, folder 1 of 2, 2007 September 21 (Box 18, Folder 20-26)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs Freedom of Information Act responses - Nipmuc 69A, folder 1 of 2, 2007 September 21 (Box 19, Folder 1-3)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs Freedom of Information Act responses - Nipmuc 69A, folder 2 of 2, undated (Box 19, Folder 4-8)
    - Final Determination Against Federal Acknowledgment of the Nipmuc Nation, 2004 June 25 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - In RE Federal Acknowledgment of the Nipmuc Nation, 2007 September 4 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Nipmuc BIA GTKY file 1, 2000-2002 (Box 19, Folder 11-14)
    - Nipmuc BIA GTKY file 2, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 15-16)
    - Proposal Finding Against Federal Acknowledgment of the Nipmuc Nation, 2001 October 1 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Transcript of Technical Assistance Meeting, 2002 January 23 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1997-2007
    - Correspondence, 1997-2002 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - miscellaneous, 2005-2007 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Subject Files, circa 1745-2007; bulk 1970-2007
    - 1869 Massachusetts Act to Enfranchise Indians, 1997-2002; photocopy 2007 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Gookin. Historical Collections of the Indians in New England, 1970; photocopy 2002 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Massachusetts Commission on Indian Affairs, file I, circa 1977-2001 (Box 19, Folder 23-26)
    - Massachusetts Commission on Indian Affairs, file II, circa 1977-2001 (Box 19, Folder 27-29)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1745-2003, undated (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
    - Nipmuc Federal Recognition Petition Supplement, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Nipmuc miscellaneous - research, correspondence, press, circa 1972-2005 (Box 20, Folder 4-5)
    - Nipmuc petition 69A interested parties records, circa 2000-2005 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Nipmuc research, circa 1999-2006, undated (Box 20, Folder 7-10)
    - Research - bibliographic records, 2002-2005 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Shadow of the Great Hill, excerpt, 2002-2005; photocopies 2007 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Press Files, circa 2001-2007
    - Clippings, circa 2001-2004, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Lakes Gaming, 2007 May 10 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, circa 2000
    - Kevin Gover, former Assistant Secretary Indian Affairs Bureau of Indian Affairs (BIA), with Norma (?) Fox-Gould and William W. Gould, Sr., circa 2000; photocopies (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Series 8. Schaghticoke, circa 1666-2006; bulk 1997-2006
  - Legal Documents, 2005-2006
    - Declaration of Aurene Michele Martin, 2006 July 18 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Memorandum in Opposition to Motion to Intervene, Civil Action No. 3:06-CV-00081(PCD), 2006 April 7 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Memorandum of Law in Support of Motion to Intervene, Civil Action No. 3:06-CV-00081(PCD), 2006 March 17 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Motion to Intervene, Civil Action No. 3:06-CV-00081(PCD), 2006 March 17 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Petition for Review, 2006 January 12 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Reply to Memorandum in Opposition to Motion to Intervene, Civil Action No. 3:06-CV-00081(PCD), 2006 April 24 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Ruling on Motion to Intervene, Civil Action No. 3:06-CV-00081(PCD), 2006 June 14 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Ruling on Pending Motions, Case No. 3:06cv81(PCD), 2006 November 3 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - The State of Connecticut's, Kent School's, & the CL&P Company's Response to Plaintiff's Motion for Permission to Conduct Limited Discovery, 2005 March 9 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Bureau of Indian Affairs, 2002-2003
    - Comments of the State of Connecticut, the CL&P Company, Kent School Corporation, and Town of Kent on the Proposed Finding on the Petition for Federal Tribal Acknowledgment of the Schaghticoke Tribal Nation Petitioner Group, 2003 August 8 (Box 20, Folder 25-26)
    - Summary Under the Criteria and Evidence for Proposed Finding Schaghticoke Tribal Nation, 2002 December 5 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Reports, 1997-1998
    - 20th Century Addendum to the April, 1997 Petition of the Schaghticoke Tribal Nation for Federal Acknowledgment, 1998 March 20 (Box 20, Folder 28-29)
    - Anthropological Report Supplementing the Petition of the Schaghticoke Tribal Nation of Kent, Connecticut for Federal Acknowledgment, 1997 April (Box 20, Folder 30-32)
    - Federal Acknowledgment Petition, 83.7(a) Mandatory Criteria for Federal Acknowledgment - Statement of Facts, undated (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Genealogical Report Supplementing the Petition of the Schaghticoke Tribal Nation of Kent, Connecticut for Federal Acknowledgment, 1997 April (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Historical Report Supplementing the Petition of the Schaghticoke Trible Nation of Kent, Connecticut for Federal Acknowledgment, 1997 April (Box 20, Folder 35-38)
    - Historical Report Supplementing the Petition of the Schaghticoke Trible Nation of Kent, Connecticut for Federal Acknowledgment, 1997 April (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Summary of Evidence Supplementing the Petition of the Schaghticoke Tribal Nation of Kent, Connecticut for Federal Acknowledgment, 1997 April (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1976-1993
    - Correspondence - Appalachian Trail Settlement, circa 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - Indian Claims Commission to Collier, Cristopher, esq., 1976 May 28; photocopy (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Subject Files, circa 1666-2005
    - Documents list from Day, Barry & Howard, undated (Box 21, Folder 5-9)
    - Memorandum - Schaefer, Daniel R. to Kohler, Mark F. RE: STN IBIA Reconsideration request, 2004 April 12 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Research materials, circa 1666-2005, undated; photocopies (Box 21, Folder 11-13)
- Series 9. Webster/Dudley Band of Chaubunagungamaug Nipmuck Indians, circa 1952-2008; bulk 2001-2007
  - Bureau of Indian Affairs, 2001-2007
    - Answer Brief of the State of Connecticut in Opposition to the Request for Reconsideration by the Webster/Dudley Band of Chaubunagungamaug Nipmuck Indians, Petitioner 69B, of the Final Determination Against Federal Acknowledgment, Docket No. IBIA 04-154-A, 2005 October 7 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs (BIA) Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) response, petition 69B, 2005 April 14 (Box 21, Folder 15-24)
    - Comments of the State of Connecticut and the Northeastern Connecticut Council of Governments on the Proposed Findings of the Petition for Tribal Acknowledgment of the Nipmuc Nation and the Webster/Dudley Band Chaubunagungamaug Nipmuck Indians, 2002 September 30 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Final Determination Against Federal Acknowledgment of the Webster/Dudley Band Chaubunagungamaug Nipmuck Indians, 2004 June 25 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) request - report of investigation, 2007 September 25 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Order Affirming Final Determination and Referring One Issue to the Secretary of the Interior, Docket No. IBIA 04-154-A, 2007 September 4 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Proposed Findings Against Federal Acknowledgment of the Webster/Dudley Band of Chaubunagungamaug Nipmuck Indians, 2001 October 1 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - State of Connecticut's Response Brief Regarding Interested Party Status of Tribal Member Derek Little Raven Henries, Docket No. IBIA 04-155-A, 2004 December 17 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 2004-2005
    - Correspondence - Bureau of Indian Affairs, Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) request, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Subject Files, circa 1952-2008
    - Henries request and documents, 69B, 2004-2008 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Research materials, circa 1952-2005, undated (Box 21, Folder 33-34)
- Series 10. National Archives Microfilm, 1722-1906; bulk 1800-1870
  - Letters sent by the Secretary of War relating to Military Affairs, 1800-1889 National Archives film series M-6, [15 films of a 110 roll series]
    - Vol. 1, 1800 November 12-1803 June 21 (Box 22, Folder 6-1)
    - Vol. 2, 1803 June 21-1806 April 30 (Box 22, Folder 6-2)
    - Vol. 3, 1806 May 1-1808 December 31 (Box 22, Folder 6-3)
    - Vol. 4, 1808 December 15-1810 November 12 (Box 22, Folder 6-4)
    - Vol. 5, 1810 November 13-1812 June 29 (Box 22, Folder 6-5)
    - Vol. 6, 1812 July 1-1813 June 29 (Box 22, Folder 6-6)
    - Vol. 7, 1813 July 1-1814 December 20 (Box 22, Folder 6-7)
    - Vol. 8, 1814 December 22-1816 April 29 (Box 22, Folder 6-8)
    - Vol. 9, 1816 May 2-1818 January 31 (Box 22, Folder 6-9)
    - Vol. 10, 1818 February 2-1820 October 19 (Box 22, Folder 6-10)
    - Vol. 11, 1820 February 21-1823 October 9 (Box 22, Folder 6-11)
    - Vol. 12, 1823 October 13-1830 August 10 (Box 22, Folder 6-12)
    - Vol. 13, 1830 August 7-1833 December 31 (Box 22, Folder 6-13)
    - Vol. 14, 1834 January 2-1836 January 18 (Box 22, Folder 6-14)
    - Vol. 15, 1836 January 19-May 25 (Box 22, Folder 6-15)
  - Records of the Office of the Secretary of War, Letters sent-Indian Affairs, 1800-1824 National Archives film series M-15, [6 films of a 6 roll series]
    - Vol. A, 1800 November 17-1804 April 20 (Box 22, Folder 15-1)
    - Vol. B, 1804 April 23-1809 July 5 (Box 22, Folder 15-2)
    - Vol. C, 1809 July 8-1816 December 31 (Box 22, Folder 15-3)
    - Vol. D, 1817 January 8-1820 July 31 (Box 22, Folder 15-4)
    - Vol. E, 1820 August 3-1823 October 25 (Box 22, Folder 15-5)
    - Vol. F, 1823 October 28-1824 April 26 (Box 22, Folder 15-6)
  - Letters sent by the Office of Indian Affairs, 1824-1881 National Archives film series M-21, [15 films of a 166 roll series]
    - Vol. 1, 1824 March-1825 May 3 (Box 22, Folder 21-1)
    - Vol. 2, 1825 May 4-1826 May 31 (Box 22, Folder 21-2)
    - Vol. 3, 1826 June 1-1827 March 31 (Box 22, Folder 21-3)
    - Vol. 4, 1827 April-1828 June 5 (Box 22, Folder 21-4)
    - Vol. 5, 1828 June 5-1829 June 7 (Box 22, Folder 21-5)
    - Vol. 6, 1829 June 8-1830 July 30 (Box 22, Folder 21-6)
    - Vol. 7, 1830 August-1831 December 31 (Box 22, Folder 21-7)
    - Vol. 8, 1832 January 1-July 4 (Box 22, Folder 21-8)
    - Vol. 9, 1832 July 5-1833 January 27 (Box 22, Folder 21-9)
    - Vol. 10, 1833 January 28-June 18 (Box 22, Folder 21-10)
    - Vol. 11, 1833 June 19-December 31 (Box 22, Folder 21-11)
    - Vol. 12, 1834 January 1-May 31 (Box 22, Folder 21-12)
    - Vol. 13, 1834 June 1-September 30 (Box 22, Folder 21-13)
    - Vol. 14, 1834 October 1-1835 January 31 (Box 22, Folder 21-14)
    - Vol. 15, 1835 February 1-April 28 (Box 22, Folder 21-15)
  - Domestic Letters of the Department of State, 1784-1906 National Archives film series M-40, [15 films of a 171 roll series]
    - 1788 October 10-1792 December 25 (Box 22, Folder 40-4)
    - 1792 February 4-1793 December 31 (Box 22, Folder 40-5)
    - 1794 January 2-June 26 (Box 22, Folder 40-6)
    - 1794 June 27-1794 November 30 (Box 22, Folder 40-7)
    - 1794 December 6-1795 October 12 (Box 22, Folder 40-8)
    - 1795 October 12-1797 February 28 (Box 22, Folder 40-9)
    - 1797 March 1-1798 June 29 (Box 22, Folder 40-10)
    - 1798 June 30-1799 June 29 (Box 22, Folder 40-11)
    - 1802 May 1-1805 May 30 (Box 22, Folder 40-12)
    - 1805 June 1-1810 July 21 (Box 22, Folder 40-13)
    - 1811 January 22-1817 February 18 (Box 22, Folder 40-14)
    - 1817 March 3-1820 February 23 (Box 22, Folder 40-15)
  - Letters Sent to the President by the Secretary of War, 1800-1863 National Archives film series M-127, [3 films of a 6 roll series]
    - Vol. 1, 1800 November 13-1820 January 6 (Box 22, Folder 127-1)
    - Vol. 2, 1820 January 7-1833 March 9 (Box 22, Folder 127-2)
    - Vol. 3, 1833 May 20-1840 October 19 (Box 22, Folder 127-3)
  - Miscellaneous Letters of the Department of State, 1789-1906 National Archives film series M-179A, [4 films of a 200 roll series]
    - Calendars to Miscellaneous Letters, 1789-1825 (Box 22, Folder 179-1)
    - 1789 January 1-December 29 (Box 22, Folder 179-2)
    - 1790 January 1-May 31 (Box 22, Folder 179-3)
    - 1790 June 3-December 31 (Box 23, Folder 179-4)
    - 1792 July 2-December 31 (Box 23, Folder 179-8)
  - Territorial Papers of the U.S. Senate, 1789-1873 National Archives film series M-200, [7 films of a 20 roll series]
    - Territory Northwest of the Ohio River, 1791-1813 (Box 23, Folder 200-1)
    - Territory South of the Ohio River, 1789-1808 (Box 23, Folder 200-2)
    - Indiana, 1792-1830 (Box 23, Folder 200-4)
    - Alabama, 1818-1822 (Box 23, Folder 200-8)
    - Arkansas, 1820-1836 (Box 23, Folder 200-8)